ANIKET DESHPANDE

+91 8237017150



anivira1999@gmail.com



Counseling Psychologist/ Therapist & Inclusive Educator

PROFILE

Aniket Deshpande is a Trauma Informed Counseling Psychologist with over 3 years of experience of working with diverse populations, from children to middle aged, and facilitating them to address their needs and concerns. He is dedicated to creating a safe and supportive environment for individuals to explore and heal from their unpleasant and disturbing experiences. His approach integrates client-centered, trauma informed, somatic, attachment based, mindfulness, cognitive and compassion; with an understanding of each person's unique journey and abilities.

EDUCATION

Family & Marriage Counseling, Aug 2022

MKSSS's Baya Karve, Pune

MA Counseling Psychology, June 2022

Sir Parashurambhau College, Pune

BA Psychology, June 2020

Sir Parashurambhau College, Pune

TRAININGS

- DARe (Prafulta)
- ISP (Prafulta)
- Trauma Informed Care (TISS, Mumbai)
- RE-CBT (IPH, Pune)
- SFBT (ASFAR)
- Remedial Teacher Training (Dhruv Foundation)
- EFT (CORE)
- Therapeutic Art Coach (Manomantra)

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

COUNSELING PSYCHOLOGIST

ROCKET HEALTH INDIA, BENGALURU | FEBRUARY 2024 - PRESENT

SCHOOL COUNSELLOR (MOU w. Dhruv Foundation)

SPM ENGLISH MEDIUM SCHOOL, PUNE | JULY 2024 - PRESENT

COUNSELING PSYCHOLOGIST & INCLUSIVE EDUCATOR

DHRUV FOUNDATION, PUNE | JULY 2022 - PRESENT

SCHOOL COUNSELLOR (MOU w. Dhruv Foundation)

NEW ENGLISH MEDIUM SCHOOL, PUNE | JULY 2023 - JANUARY 2024

INCLUSIVE EDUCATOR (MOU w. Dhruv Foundation)

KEM HOSPITAL, PUNE | AUGUST 2022 - DECEMBER 2022

PSYCHOLOGIST

MY MIND MATTERS, PUNE | AUGUST 2022 - DECEMBER 2022

VOLUNTEERING

- Trauma Informed Care while Working with Children, 2023
- Good Touch Bad Touch 360° (Jnana Prabodhini Institute, Pune), 2023
- Mental Health Awareness for Children, 2022